- id: ckw-l32-5419
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - チョコレート
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5425
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - キロカロリー
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5430
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - チップ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5449
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ペーパー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5452
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ログ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5456
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - チャレンジ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5488
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ヘア
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5493
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - リンク
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5538
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - デジカメ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5541
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アプリケーション
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5554
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - マナー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5562
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - センス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5569
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - クリニック
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5579
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - スタジオ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l32-5604
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - タッチ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []
